freebeemart.com 2018-02-22

# 

"Freebeemart" is one of the largest loyalty program in India. To offer best services to our members, we may seek information from the members time to time. This is solely for the purpose of making the program more meaningful. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our members and their transactions. This section explains how we protect and use your information in safe, secure and responsible manner because we value your privacy. 

#### 1.Protection of customer data is our priority: 

Setting policies and procedures for carefully handling members' information Protection against unauthorized access to customer data High quality authentication and virus detection technology Our service providers comply with privacy laws 

#### 2.Information collected 

We collect and use various types of information from members to service them better. Customer information shall be collected under the following categories.

#### 3.Personally Identifiable Information or (PII):

PII refers to any information that can be used to identify you as an individual in any way. Enrolment in the Freebeemart Program is contingent upon your agreeing to the terms of service and providing basic registration information, including: name, email address, mobilwe number, among others. Members will need to provide freebeemart with the basic personal identification information, wherever required, to avail of all the benefits associated with the program. 

#### 4.Profiling Information: 

Apart from the above we shall also solicit and collect from the members, time to time details on their preferences, subscription to particular news segments or offers and other promotional activities we do. The decision to participate in such activities is at the sole discretion of the member. 

#### 5.Transaction history within the program: 

Freebeemart is capable of and will collect information on transactions linked to the Freebeemart account and required for processing of Freebeemart Points, credits and debits to member's accounts. By definition this shall include all transactions on the Website, at the Freebeemart.

Partners, all promotional campaigns through emails, SMS or any other communication channel, at any other participating affiliates, subsidiary, program partners, surveys and more.

#### In some situations, however, we are required to or we may provide all information we collect about you to third parties outside our group companies, as permitted by law, such as, with your consent: 

To respond to judicial process, or

To consumer reporting agencies; or

In connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, or transfer of all or portion of business; or 

To protect against fraud, money laundering or other risks 

Some of the data may have to be provided to third party services for the sole purpose of implementing marketing services and for providing customer support services like sending statements. 

#### 6.Information Storage 

If we use a trusted third party data processors to organise, process, clean & analyse our data to help us better understand the trends and segments within our member base, all such third parties shall be bound by a non-disclosure agreement to maintain the confidentiality of the information shared and will not share the personal information any further or for purposes beyond our specific authorization. 

In case of redemption offers requiring mailing of vouchers or gift items or rewards to your mailing address, we shall have to part with your personally identifiable information to the extent required, with the redemption fulfilment vendor for delivery of orders and gift certificates. As stated before, strict compliance with a non-disclosure agreement will be sought. Such redemption vendor will not share the personally identifiable information any further or for purposes beyond our specific authorization. 

We offer you the choice to participate in offers from our partners. It is your decision whether or not to share your personally identifiable information with them. We recommend you to carefully read privacy policy of our partners before divulging your personally identifiable information, as we will not be held liable for the information practices of third-parties. Members may receive promotional offers and campaign details by email among other means. If you have opted to receive promotional offers there will be unsubscribe options with all such category of offers and members can choose to unsubscribe from such offers at any time by following the mentioned procedures. 

Selectively, members may also receive program offers via your landline or postal mail. Such contacts may result in rewards being issued to the member. We also contact you via email for administrative purposes, such as program change notifications or if we update our privacy promise. While you can elect to stop receiving email for promotional offers (as described above), you cannot unsubscribe from these administrative messages while enrolled in the program. Our member care department may contact you in response to an enquiry you submit. Member care may also contact you in regard to a particular problem that may have occurred with your account or with an offer in which you might have participated. We might use this information to learn further about your participation in the program and make it more relevant to your interests. 

#### 7.Information access by member

We respect your privacy and are committed to ensuring the confidentiality of your information with us. We may contact you with useful information on products and services through our telemarketing / tele calling activities, which may be beneficial for you. We may also send you newsletters regularly. 

However, if you do not wish to be contacted through our telemarketing calls or messages, newsletters, we request you to kindly register at our contact centre and give details of the telephone on which you do not wish to be contacted. 

Freebeemart is committed to follow the laws laid out with regards to tele calling and telemarketing and, does follow the guidelines set by any regulatory authority like TRAI in cases of DND policy or any such similar rule which may be in force. 

Once you have registered for any such DND policy: 

Your telephone number(s) will be removed from all our telemarketing calling lists within 30 working days. 

We will ensure that you do not get any further telemarketing calls on the telephone number(s) that you have registered

#### 8.Aggregate Data: We do not provide any of your personally identifiable information to our advertisers. 

Because we contact you on their behalf, they do not have access to your personally identifiable information unless you make the choice to share it with them. We may share non-personally identifiable information collected via the program in aggregate (or grouped), anonymous form with advertisers or other third parties so that they may better evaluate what products and services are most appealing to different segments of our member base, but we do not disclose your personally identifiable information to these third parties without your consent. 

#### 9.Anti-Spam Policy: 

Because email is an integral part of the program, your sharing of email contact with us allows us to share the program information, offers and promotions via email with you. If you later decide you wish to cease participation in this portion of the program, you may do so at any time by unsubscribing to our communication. Please note that opting not to receive email does not exempt you from receiving administrative emails that include but are not limited to, notices about vital program and membership status changes or alterations to our terms of service or any other service requests, redemption orders placed with us. 

#### 10.Security of Information

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect customer information. Specific employees are authorized to access customer information on a need to know basis for business purposes only. Our employees are bound by code of ethics that requires confidential treatment of customer information and are subject to disciplinary action if they fail to follow this code. 

#### 11.Please provide accurate information:

It is in your interest and it is our objective, to have accurate, current and complete information concerning you and your account. We have strict procedures that our employees abide by to meet this objective. While some procedures are required by Central, State or RBI regulations, we have implemented additional procedures to maintain accurate, correct and complete financial information, including processes to update information and remove outdated information. If you believe that we have incorrect information about you or your accounts, please intimate us. We will correct any erroneous information as soon as possible

#### 12.Grievance cell:

In the event you have any queries or issues in relation to collection or usage of your personal information, please contact support@freebeemart.com

#### About Freebeemart.com:

Freebeemart is one of the largest loyalty programs in India. Under this program, BSNL customers collect loyalty Points when they pay their bills and recharge talktime. The customers earn more Points when they do their regular shopping. 

All you have to do is to go to your favourite store through Freebeemart. Then do your regular shopping. You get best deals and earn reward points from Freebeemart. 

For example, if you want to shop for a shirt, go to 

[_www.freebeemart.com_](http://www.freebeemart.com/) first and access your favorite store (say, Flipkart) from [_www.freebeemart.com_](http://www.freebeemart.com/). Do your regular shopping and we will give you Reward points. 

Once you add up reward points, you can redeem the points against Gift Vouchers of 140 stores. You can shop at these 140 stores using the gift vouchers.
